cezannehr.com 2017-09-04

# HR Software Systems - HR Website Terms of Use | Cezanne HR

Cezanne HR is committed to safeguarding your privacy. This privacy policy statement outlines the data processing practices relating to our website, [www.cezannehr.com](https://cezannehr.com/), and any of our associated websites. If you have any questions regarding this statement please contact us.

## Consent

By using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described below.

We gather information about visitors to our website in two ways:

  * Directly, for example when you register for a demonstration or request information about any of our products and services;
  * or indirectly, through our site technology.

## Information collected directly

We use the information that you provide when you request information about our products or services to satisfy that request. In some instances, this information will be forwarded to one of our partners who is in a better position, because of geographic or other considerations, to satisfy your request.

We may use the email or address information that you have provided to us through the registration and information forms, to send promotional emails or direct mail about product updates or new services offered by Cezanne HR.

If you wish to opt out of receiving this information please contact us.

We do not sell, or make available, your information to other third parties.

## Information collected indirectly

When you access [www.cezannehr.com](https://cezannehr.com/) or any of our associated websites, we may collect information about your computer and your visit, such as your internet (IP) address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages visited. We may use this information in the administration of our websites, to improve the websites’ usability, and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you.

## Use of cookies

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to your web browser and stored on your computer. This enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Further information on the use of cookies can be found at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

Internet browsers normally accept cookies by default, but it is possible to set a browser to reject cookies. Cookies which have already been set, can be deleted from your hard drive.

To learn more about how to reject cookies, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or go to the help menu within your internet browser.

## Google Analytics cookies

Google Analytics is a website monitoring tool that allows users to see volumes of website visitors, their source, and to analyse how the content of their website is viewed and navigated. This in turn allows optimisation of the content and pages on [www.cezannehr.com](https://cezannehr.com/) the marketing programs that drive traffic to the website. Google Analytics does not store any personal information about website visitors, but does use persistent cookies to identify repeat visitors. You may universally opt-out of all Google Analytics tracking used by all websites by visiting the following url <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

## Social network cookies

Some pages on our website(s) contain social network ‘share’ or ‘like’ buttons. The social network may set a cookie (or cookies) on your PC when you click on one of these buttons.

In order to implement these buttons on our website(s) we use code which is hosted by the relevant social network. If you are a member of some of these networks they may use this code to track that you have visited our website(s) whether you click the buttons or not.

## Emails

We use third party providers to deliver our marketing emails. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies including clear gifs to help us monitor and improve our email marketing. You have the option to opt out of future mailings, or to change your subscription preferences. Information on how to do this is usually given at the bottom of the email.

## Access to information

You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you. If we do, you have the right to access that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. Please contact us for further information.

## Security

This site is maintained by Cezanne HR. Cezanne HR maintains appropriate measures to ensure that users’ personal details are not misused within the Cezanne HR server environment.

## Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing [www.cezannehr.com](https://cezannehr.com/) and associated websites and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

## Links to other sites

The [www.cezannehr.com](https://cezannehr.com/) website contains links to other websites. Cezanne HR is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such Web Sites.

This privacy statement was last updated on 1st March 2013\. Privacy policy may change from time to time. All changes to the policy will be posted to the website and are effective as of posting.
